foxmoviestv.com 2018-10-09

# Fox Networks Group Middle East

##  Privacy Policy

**1\. Applicability:** This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) is applicable to any personal information, which is given by you via the Site located at http://foxarabia.tv (the “Site”) operated by FOX International Channels FZ LLC (“FM”). This Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details.

**2\. Data Collection:** When using the Site You may encounter areas such as games, competitions or video services where you may be asked to enter personal information. Such information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected, for any other purposes specified at the collection point and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise stated, FM does not trade on any personal information collected by us.

**3\. FOX Middle East use of your data:** By entering personal information, you accept that FM may retain such information or transfer such information to other computer servers in other countries and that it may be held by FM or any third party company which processes it on FM's behalf. Without prejudice to the generality of paragraph two above, FM shall be entitled to use your personal information for the following purposes:

**i.** Market research, including statistical analysis of user behavior which FM may disclose to third parties in depersonalized, aggregated form.

**ii.** In order to enable FM to comply with any requirements imposed on FM by law.

**iii.** Where permitted by law, in order to send you periodic communications (this may include e-mail), about features, products and services, events and special offers. Such communications from FM may include advertising for third party companies or organizations.

**4\. Analysis of User Behavior:** We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request personal information and you should check the applicable privacy policy of that party.

**5\. Cookies:** You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of small text files that store basic information that a Site can use to recognize repeat site visits and as an example, recall your name if this has been previously supplied ("Cookies"). FM may use Cookies to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site, target the advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising. Cookies from the Site do not attach to your system and damage your files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. Note, however, that any personalized services may be affected if the Cookie option is disabled.

**6\. Updates:** Please email FM at Feedback to notify FM of any changes to the personal information you have previously provided.

**7 Transfer of Information:** The Information may be transferred by us to our computer servers in other countries given the global nature of our business.

**8\. Amendments:** FM may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting changes online. Please review these changes regularly. Your continued use of the Site will be deemed an acceptance of the privacy policy existing at that time. If at any time You are not agreeable to the terms of the privacy policy, your only recourse is to discontinue the usage of the Site.
